{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Electrical Installation \u0026 Rough-In Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/39774/":{"taskOID":39774,"originalTaskOID":39774,"setID":307,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500241,"questionDisplayText":"Project description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes your electrical project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes your electrical project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200363,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Complete wiring for addition or remodel","answerDisplayText":"Complete wiring for addition or remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200364,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electrical panel upgrade only","answerDisplayText":"Electrical panel upgrade only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200365,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Update or add a few fixtures, outlets or switches","answerDisplayText":"Update or add a few fixtures, outlets or switches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5578,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms Included","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What area(s) of the home will be included in this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3630,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Living, Family, or Dining rooms","answerDisplayText":"Living, Family, or Dining rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3477,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Laundry or utility room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry or utility room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2721,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garage or Basement","answerDisplayText":"Garage or Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4613,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Patio or outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Patio or outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4352,"questionDisplayText":"Electrical Devices","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which types of electrical devices will you need wired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6229,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Switches (standard)","answerDisplayText":"Switches (standard)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall outlets","answerDisplayText":"Wall outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2536,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor outlets","answerDisplayText":"Floor outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1861,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dedicated circuits","answerDisplayText":"Dedicated circuits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6209,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Surge protection","answerDisplayText":"Surge protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2034,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Doorbell","answerDisplayText":"Doorbell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6269,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Telephone/modem line","answerDisplayText":"Telephone/modem line","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3602,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Lightning protection","answerDisplayText":"Lightning protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5940,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Specialty lighting","answerDisplayText":"Specialty lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1292,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Ceiling fixtures/fans","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling fixtures/fans","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":887,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Attic/Whole house fans","answerDisplayText":"Attic/Whole house fans","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5912,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Spa","answerDisplayText":"Spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500241,"questionDisplayText":"Project description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes your electrical project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes your electrical project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200363,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Complete wiring for addition or remodel","answerDisplayText":"Complete wiring for addition or remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200364,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electrical panel upgrade only","answerDisplayText":"Electrical panel upgrade only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200365,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Update or add a few fixtures, outlets or switches","answerDisplayText":"Update or add a few fixtures, outlets or switches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200363,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Complete wiring for addition or remodel","answerDisplayText":"Complete wiring for addition or remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200364,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electrical panel upgrade only","answerDisplayText":"Electrical panel upgrade only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200365,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Update or add a few fixtures, outlets or switches","answerDisplayText":"Update or add a few fixtures, outlets or switches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5578,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms Included","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What area(s) of the home will be included in this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3630,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Living, Family, or Dining rooms","answerDisplayText":"Living, Family, or Dining rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3477,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Laundry or utility room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry or utility room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2721,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garage or Basement","answerDisplayText":"Garage or Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4613,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Patio or outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Patio or outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3630,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Living, Family, or Dining rooms","answerDisplayText":"Living, Family, or Dining rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3477,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Laundry or utility room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry or utility room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2721,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garage or Basement","answerDisplayText":"Garage or Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4613,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Patio or outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Patio or outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4352,"questionDisplayText":"Electrical Devices","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which types of electrical devices will you need wired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6229,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Switches (standard)","answerDisplayText":"Switches (standard)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall outlets","answerDisplayText":"Wall outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2536,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor outlets","answerDisplayText":"Floor outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1861,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dedicated circuits","answerDisplayText":"Dedicated circuits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6209,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Surge protection","answerDisplayText":"Surge protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2034,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Doorbell","answerDisplayText":"Doorbell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6269,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Telephone/modem line","answerDisplayText":"Telephone/modem line","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3602,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Lightning protection","answerDisplayText":"Lightning protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5940,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Specialty lighting","answerDisplayText":"Specialty lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1292,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Ceiling fixtures/fans","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling fixtures/fans","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":887,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Attic/Whole house fans","answerDisplayText":"Attic/Whole house fans","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5912,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Spa","answerDisplayText":"Spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6229,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Switches (standard)","answerDisplayText":"Switches (standard)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall outlets","answerDisplayText":"Wall outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2536,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor outlets","answerDisplayText":"Floor outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1861,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dedicated circuits","answerDisplayText":"Dedicated circuits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6209,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Surge protection","answerDisplayText":"Surge protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2034,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Doorbell","answerDisplayText":"Doorbell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6269,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Telephone/modem line","answerDisplayText":"Telephone/modem line","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3602,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Lightning protection","answerDisplayText":"Lightning protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5940,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Specialty lighting","answerDisplayText":"Specialty lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1292,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Ceiling fixtures/fans","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling fixtures/fans","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":887,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Attic/Whole house fans","answerDisplayText":"Attic/Whole house fans","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5912,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Spa","answerDisplayText":"Spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/39774/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":39774,"taskName":"Electrical for Home Addition or Remodel - Install","taskDescription":"Install Electrical for a Home Addition or Remodel","xmTaskDescriptor":"Electrical Installation \u0026 Rough-In Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":167,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Addition Remodel wire wiring","textMessagingName":"Remodel Electrical","rolloverLongDesc":"This includes running all standard wiring \u0026 components in new structures, additions \u0026 remodeled spaces. Note separate categories for running wires \u0026 components in already finished spaces, landscape lighting \u0026 for heavy ups.","rolloverShortDesc":"Wiring for new structures and remodels","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Electrical for a Home Addition or Remodel.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Electrical Installation \u0026 Rough-In \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Electrical for Additions, Remodels","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":25,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Home Addition or Remodel Electrical Installation","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Electrical for Home Addition or Remodel - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Electrician Need","urlName":"Electrical-for-Home-Addition-or-Remodel-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Electrical Installation \u0026 Rough-In Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Addition,electric,Remodel,wire,wiring,electrician","emcCategoryOid":-12026,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":307,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}